Narrator: 1
Rooms
A: a bathroom
Narrator: 5
B: a bedroom
Narrator: 7
A: a dining room
Narrator: 10
B: a garage
Narrator: 1
A: a half bathroom
Narrator: 8
B: a hall
Narrator: 9
A: a kitchen
Narrator: 3
B: a living room
Narrator: 2
A: a study / an office
Narrator: 6
B: a yard
Narrator: 2
Parts of a room
A: a balcony
Narrator: 11
B: a ceiling
Narrator: 15
A: a floor
Narrator: 14
B: stairs
Narrator: 13
A: a wall
Narrator: 3
Things in a room
B: an armchair
Narrator: 23
A: a bathtub
Narrator: 26
B: a bed
Narrator: 29
A: a cupboard
Narrator: 32
B: a dishwasher
Narrator: 21
A: a fireplace
Narrator: 18
B: a light
Narrator: 30
A: a microwave
Narrator: 16
B: a mirror
Narrator: 19
A: a plant
Narrator: 28
B: a refrigerator / a fridge
Narrator: 27
A: a rug
Narrator: 17
B: a shelf
Narrator: 24
A: a shower
Narrator: 33
B: a sink
Narrator: 20
A: a sofa / a couch
Narrator: 34
B: a stove
Narrator: 25
A: a wardrobe
Narrator: 31
B: a washing machine